♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we’ve got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright
on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we’ll
withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there
when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we
will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko
stronger after all ♪
(SINISTER MUSIC)
As I’m sure you’ve noticed, this sheet
of titanium is much stronger than steel,
which is why it is used by NASA
for constructing its space shuttles.
You should’ve used it for your robot.
I’m afraid this alloy would be
a bit out of your budget range, Herb.
But since your friend brought up
the subject, let me remind you
that the robot competition
is scheduled for this afternoon.
I hope you’ve all finished your models!
Is yours ready, Jeremie?
Mhmm.
And you, Herb?
No problem. Come and see
my masterpiece after school, okay?
(SINISTER MUSIC)
Well let me see it, Herb. I’m waiting.
Tada!
Aaaaah!
What is that--that horror!
Well, it’s our team’s robot.
Iron Sissi.
Huh? What! How dare you name
that hideous robot after me!
But it’s a tribute to you!
And besides, it may be ugly,
but watch how it works!
Oh, Herb, Herb! Do something!
It’s nothing!
Couple of adjustments,
and it’ll be just fine.
It better be!
If not, Jeremie and his pals
are gonna humiliate you again!
It’s gonna win, ugly or not!
And if it doesn’t,
say goodbye to Sissi’s gang!
That goes for you too, Nicholas!
Nothing to worry about.
I’ve thought of everything.
I’d like you to meet Kiwi Two.
That’s cool! Kiwi’s got a playmate!
He’s as cute as the original!
Congratulations!
Yeah! How’s our nice little robot, hm?
You want a bolt or a nut?
Sorry.
I didn’t have the time to take him out.
He needs an oil change every day!
(LAUGHING, SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
Hey, it’s time.
Here we go! We’re bound for glory, guys!
See you later, Aelita.
Call us if you see or hear
anything suspicious on Lyoko.
I promise.
But I hope XANA gives you
enough time to win the contest!
Bye-bye!
And now, the moment
you’ve all been waiting for!
That’s right, folks! The grand finale!
In this corner, Iron Sissi!
And in this corner, Kiwi Two!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
Kiwi Two! Kiwi Two!
Jeremie versus Herb.
Boy, isn’t that original.
And the winner will be Jeremie.
Boy, what suspense.
Remember, both robots are forbidden
to use any physical force.
Shake hands, now!
Let’s roll!
The first to score five baskets
is the winner!
Let’s go!
(CHEERING)
Hey, Jeremie!
Can you hear me?
Jeremie!
Yeah! Great! Kiwi one, Sissi zero!
(CHEERING)
Very good,
but I’ve never seen a robot so ugly!
Dad!
Jeremie!
Jeremie, please answer!
Way to go, Jeremie! Way to go!
Keep it up, dude!
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
Timeout!
One minute for halftime.
You’re doing great, Jeremie! Keep it up!
(CHEERING)
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
Game ball!
Oh, no! I don’t believe it!
(CHEERING)
Go on, Kiwi! Go on!
Yeah!
Ready, set…
(CACKLES)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
We won! We won! Oh, we really did it!
Uh…well done! And thank you
to all our contestants!
The robot contest is over for this year!
And remember, class 9B,
you’ve got Phys Ed in five minutes!
It’s okay, Jeremie.
Don’t worry about it.
You can’t win all the time.
But what happened?
We could show you!
Take a look at this!
So that was it.
He cheated us.
Well, am I still a part of the gang,
or what, huh?
I guess. We did win, but it’s still
the ugliest robot I’ve ever seen.
Herb? Can I see you for a minute?
(SCREAMING)
Huh!
Where did that come from!
I’m getting outta here!
Aaah!
Come on!
Hey, yo! What are you doing in here!
You gotta get out.
You thinking what I’m thinking?
XANA.
If it’s true, Aelita’s probably
been trying to reach us.
Aelita?
Jeremie! At last!
Everything okay?
No, not really.
XANA’s activated a tower,
and the Bloks are after me.
And we’ve got a humongous robot at school
that’s causing total panic
wherever it goes.
But how could XANA have
ever made a thing like that?
I wish I knew, but one thing is sure--
it’s us he’s after.
Okay, Ulrich and Yumi,
you’ve got to try neutralizing that thing
while Odd and I go to the factory
to give Aelita some help.
Better hurry.
Let’s go.
Good luck, you two, and stay in contact.
Ready?
Ready.
Hey, it looks like our visitor
has already gone to the factory.
It might be much worse.
-He could’ve been made there!
Look at that!
He won’t quit!
I can’t access anything.
All the programs, the scanners,
the holomap--nothing!
Everything’s down.
That means I can’t send you to Lyoko.
Got any ideas?
Not really.
We should try to find
a specialist in robots.
Hey, Ulrich.
Jeremie! How are you doing?
Not so great.
XANA made a robot on the
assembly line at the factory.
And he messed up all the controls.
No way of getting to Lyoko.
The time’s come to eliminate the robot.
Jeremie’s too busy.
Jeremie’s not the only one
who knows about robots.
Who have you got in mind?
Herb.
We haven’t got a choice, I guess.
Quick, we gotta find him.
Odd, plug in the IDE.
It’s done.
Bingo! You’re a genius, Jeremie.
You’re coming with us.
Hey, where are you going! Come back!
The school’s being evacuated! Aaaah!
Herb, we’ve got a favor to ask you.
Will you help us disconnect that robot?
I’m sorry, but you’re not in my gang.
It’s a tremendous danger, Herb.
I said no.
I wonder what Sissi’d think
if she found out you were a cheater.
What?
Milly and Tamiya have it all on tape.
Positive proof.
Okay.
But if you tell her--
You stay with Herb.
I’ll take care of this guy.
Come on, Herb.
Hey, you’d better find a way
to eliminate this horror.
I may have an idea,
but we’ll need Missus Hertz’s drill.
Jeremie!
I finally found the activated tower!
You can’t go by yourself!
I’ll go.
Okay, but I don’t know if the scanner
management program is operational
It’s too late to test it!
Let’s give it a try!
The mountain region
is where you’re headed, Odd.
Transfer Odd.
Scanner Odd.
Virtualization.
Odd, are you okay?
Fine. I made it, Jeremie.
That’s great.
Aelita’s just a little further north.
There we are.
Let’s hope the robot’s
not made of titanium.
Aelita!
There.
We’d better make a little detour.
Ah!
XANA, no.
No. Don’t hurt him.
Hey, Ulrich!
We got him.
Behind you!
Laser arrow!
Watch out, Odd!
Odd, only 50 life points left.
Thanks, Jeremie, but who’s counting?
Are you alright?
The second one’s coming!
Herb, I’ve gotta hand it to you,
your droid worked miracles.
Thank you.
Well, I’ve got to go now.
There are a couple of things
I’ve got to do.
Hey, this isn’t exactly summer camp here!
Tell Ulrich and Yumi to move it!
They’ll be there soon.
I don’t believe this!
It’s a nightmare.
We’ve got to go to Lyoko.
Jeremie, how many points?
Only 10 left.
Odd, you’ve gotta jump.
Okay, Jeremie, what’s up?
Odd’s losing all his life points.
Head for the scanner!
Right.
Oh!
It’s never gonna stop.
Get in!
Transfer Yumi.
Scanner Yumi.
Virtualization!
Okay, concentrate on the rotation speed!
Two monsters!
Go ahead. I’ll take care of the last one.
Return to the past now.
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
(CHEERING)
Game ball!
Go on, Kiwi Two!
Oh, no!
Ready, set…
Huh!
I now declare Jeremie the winner
of this year’s robot contest!
Yeah!
Okay, you two, I want both of you
to shake hands, come on.
No way!
Huh?
What a sore loser.
I forgive him.
He’s nice every now and then.
Huh? You mind explaining?
(LAUGHING)
Come on, we’ll tell you all about it.
Hm…?
I knew it!
You’re a loser, and so is your robot!
It’s as ugly as you are!
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY
REDDIT.COM/R/CODELYOKO